

Rodion P

Python developer

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native English - B1

WHO AM I?

Python / Django Developer, (over 2 years). I am a FullStack developer with experience in implementing Front-end and Backend parts. Also, I grow up my expertise up as a DevOps, gaining my experience there. In my free time, I expand my skills by studying new technologies. I develop projects with my own ideas for practice. Python experience: - Django - Python - Docker - Poetry - Typer - HTML - CSS - JavaScript - PostgreSQL - Git Currently, I am getting a higher education in the specialization "Applied informatics in economics".

SKILLS

JIRA AWS Ubuntu Linux G	Gitlab Bitbucket Git Github	Docker DevOps PostgreSQL
MySQL API Lektor Poetry	Django Python CSS HTML	C# JavaScript

EDUCATION

2019 — 2022 Bauman Moscow State Technical University

Bachelor of Computer Science (BCompSc), Computer science

EXPERIENCE

2020 — 2021 FullStack Developer

Project: E-portfolio. A service for storing and publishing the achievements of schoolchildren, students, teachers, and university employees. On this platform, the possibility of creating events, inviting participants, publishing articles, news, etc.was implemented. Also, the possibility of creating companies for holding events and joint collaborations with large companies was realized. In this project, I took the role of a Web developer. My responsibilities included the Server part and the development Interface. For the Backend part, I used Python 3.8, Django, Poetry, Docker. In the Frontend part, Semantic UI and Javascript were used.

HTML CSS Docker Django Python JavaScript Poetry

2021 — 2021 FullStack Developer

Project: Static Web Site/IT Sochi Community My main task when creating this site was to provide an opportunity for each user to quickly and, most importantly, find out about the company in an accessible way. Provide an opportunity for upcoming events in it, view certain vacancies, get acquainted with the main faces of the company, as well as view photos from the company's working account in Instagram. I was creating a static website using the Lektor technology created in the Python programming language. Templates were created with sections on the site that can be filled in using the Lektor administrative panel. Also, in this project, I used technologies such as Poetry and Python Magic. The possibility of viewing vacancies by certain parameters using the HeadHunter API was implemented, as well as the ability to view photos from the company's Instagram account.

HTML CSS Python JavaScript Lektor

2021 — 2021 **Python Developer**

Algorithm that output information in text form from any file The task of this project was to an algorithm in the Python programming language that would allow you to output informati text form from any file with the extension listed below (.csv

.doc .docx .eml .epub .gif .jpg .jpeg .json .html .mp3 .msg .odt .ogg .pdf .png .pptx .ps .rtf .. .tiff .txt .wav .xlsx .xls). This project used several technologies, for example, Poetry for mar dependencies and building packages in Python. Next, the Textract library was used. Initiall program worked when starting Docker, but then Python Typer was used to create a full-fle console application.

Docker Python Poetry Typer

2021 — 2021 FullStack Developer

Project: CV-portal. A portal for storing and publishing resumes. Everyone can create their own resume and share a unique link with another person. For an HR manager, it is possible to collect several resumes in one group and share a link to this group. User registration takes place through Google account authentication In this project, I took the role of a Web Developer, using Python, Django, Poetry, Docker, Fomantic UI, Javascript.

HTML CSS Docker Django Python JavaScript Poetry

2022 — 2022 Backend developer

Project: DefaultCV v3.0 A portal for storing and publishing resumes. Everyone can create their own resume and share a unique link with another person. For an HR manager, it is possible to collect several resumes in one group and share a link to this group. User registration takes place through Google account authentication In this project, I took the role of a Backend Developer, using python3.9, django, DRF, poetry, docker, docker-compose and dynaconf

DRF Docker PostgreSQL Python Poetry